Email LinkedIn Portfolio Github +6580433005 Singapore

SUMMARY

Full Stack developer with 4 years of experience. Independent, focused and a fast learner to deliver digital solutions to meet user needs. Proven track record of developing digital solutions ranging from proof of concepts to user facing web applications using Agile methodology.

EXPERIENCE

Airbus, Singapore — Digital Solutions Engineer

NOVEMBER 2022 - CURRENT

- Successfully delivered 4 projects in the span of 8 months as per contractual delivery requirements awarding the organization SGD1mil
- Utilized Docker and network configuration for our team's Large Language
 Model server to address data privacy concerns
- Developed a web app that standardizes aviation template into a specific structured data using React, Flask and NLP. Ongoing exploration with Large Language Models for more robust extraction over various templates
- Utilized React, Websockets, and Flask create a web app with 16 screens while integrating external IOT, enabling real-time telemetry display while ensuring seamless user experience as per project's goal
- Created and implemented UI/UX wireframes of 8 screens with Tauri for video and data processing for the project's goal of retrospective analysis
- Contributed and enhanced internal Airbus frontend library by implementing 4 new features for React and Angular

Redsquare Software, Malaysia — *Software Associate*

MAY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

- Successfully completed a project allowing the organization to have a steady stream of revenue from project completion and maintenance
- Implemented over 60 responsive screens based on user interface design using NextJS with Redux for an automotive news web platform
- Initialized CMS backend using Docker to allow the organization a head start in project delivery

SEAM LLC, Malaysia — Web/UX-Developer

MARCH 2020 - MAY 2021

- Communicated with the project members to design, develop over 30 React components and deliver features for an in-house web platform
- Improved 20+ UI/UX issues with Designer with regards to the architecture and technical feasibility of the platform

EDUCATION

Multimedia University, Malaysia — Bachelor of Computer Science (Hons.)

JUNE 2017 - MARCH 2020

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Tailwind
- Javascript / Typescript
- React / NextJS
- Redux / Zustand
- Python
- Flask
- Git / Github
- GraphQL
- Rust / Tauri
- Docker
- Amazon Web Services

LANGUAGES

- English
- Malay
- Basic Mandarin